[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
*
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
[laughing]
[笑]
- And how was
your meal today, ma'am?
- 怎么样？
女士，今天吃饭吗？
- Oh, delicious.
- 哦，好吃。
I wish I could tell everyone
我希望我能告诉大家
how great my meal was.
我的饭菜多么美味啊。
- Well, you're more then welcome
to go to each table
- 好吧，非常欢迎你
去每张桌子
and tell 'em about
your satisfactory experience.
并告诉他们
您满意的体验。
- I don't really have time
to do that.
-我真的没有时间
这样做。
Perhaps I will mention it
in my will.
也许我会提到它
在我的意愿中。
- Well, if that's the way
you want it.
- 好吧，如果是这样的话
你想要它。
- Wait!
I have an idea.
- 等待！
我有一个主意。
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
- Hold on a second.
That's me corkboard.
- 等一下。
那是我的软木板。
It's for all me...
这是为了我所有人...
memos.
备忘录。
[cash register dings]
[收银机叮叮声]
- Mr. Krabs,
think of it now as...
- 蟹老板先生，
现在把它想成...
a bulletin board
for the community,
布告栏
为社会，
a place where
a yearning populace
一个地方
向往的民众
can express themselves freely.
可以自由地表达自己。
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
[upbeat instrumental music]
[欢快的器乐]
*
Hmm.
唔。
Well, I was just gonna loiter,
嗯，我只是想闲逛，
but now I think I'll get
a Krabby Patty.
但现在我想我会得到
蟹肉饼。
*
[cash register dings]
[收银机叮叮声]
- Hey, everybody,
- 嘿，大家，
a community bulletin board
is here.
社区公告板
在这里。
Tell your friends
to come on down and use it
告诉你的朋友
下来使用它
for the good of me business--
me wallet--
为了我的生意好——
我的钱包——
[stammering]
[结巴]
I mean, the community.
我的意思是，社区。
*
[indistinct conversation]
[含糊不清的对话]
- [crying]
- [哭泣]
Community.
社区。
*
- Oh, I really hope
people like it.
- 哦，我真的希望
人们喜欢它。
*
- Number one with a star.
- 带星星的第一名。
- [laughing]
- [笑]
[wheel squeaking]
[车轮吱吱作响]
- See, Mr. Krabs?
- 看到了吗，蟹老板？
The community bulletin board
is a good thing.
社区公告栏
是一件好事。
- Yes.
Yes, it is.
- 是的。
是的。
It's bringing me closer
to my favorite part
它让我更接近
到我最喜欢的部分
of the community: their money.
社区的：他们的钱。
- Let's see what other
nice people are saying.
- 让我们看看还有什么
好人说。
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- What are you shrieking about?
- 你在尖叫什么？
- Nothing.
I just love to shriek.
- 没有什么。
我就是喜欢尖叫。
[shrieking]
[尖叫]
- Step aside, boy,
you're blocking
- 靠边站，孩子，
你正在阻止
me moneymaking bulletin board.
我赚钱的公告板。
[creaking]
[吱吱作响]
- "When I eat
at the Krusty Krab..."
-“当我吃饭的时候
在蟹堡王……”
Ouch.
哎哟。
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
Hey, not on my bulletin board.
嘿，不在我的公告板上。
- Whoa, whoa, dude,
what's with the censorship?
- 哇哦，哇哦，伙计，
审查制度怎么了？
The community bulletin board
is for everybody.
社区公告栏
适合所有人。
You can't just
take something down
你不能只是
把东西拿下来
because you think it's bogus.
因为你认为它是假的。
- Mr. Krabs,
Surfer Fish is right.
- 蟹老板先生，
冲浪者鱼是对的。
The board is sacred,
and it must be respected.
董事会是神圣的，
并且它必须受到尊重。
"Dear P-Star7,
I'm so sorry you had
“亲爱的 P-Star7，
我很抱歉你有
"a less than stellar experience
at the Krusty Krab,
“一次不太好的体验
在蟹堡王店，
"and we promise
to do better in future.
“我们保证
以便将来做得更好。
Signed, Fry-Banshee139."
签名，Fry-Banshee139。”
Ha.
Crisis averted.
哈。
危机得以避免。
Huh?
啊？
"Signed, GuyBesideU3."
“签名，GuyBesideU3。”
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
- Huh?
- 啊？
"Dumb-blurted, LOL?"
“哑口无言，哈哈？”
"What's the point?"
“有什么意义？”
"I could make a better patty
out of mud"?
“我可以做出更好的肉饼
从泥里出来”？
Where are all these notes
coming from?
这些笔记都在哪里
来自？
- Pencils, paper.
- 铅笔、纸。
Pencils, paper.
铅笔、纸。
- I want to express
the worst side of myself.
- 我想表达
我自己最糟糕的一面。
- [chuckling]
- [轻笑]
Why not?
为什么不呢？
And don't forget
to feed your hatred
并且不要忘记
来满足你的仇恨
with a selection
from our menu.
有选择
从我们的菜单中。
- Huh?
Oh.
- 啊？
哦。
- If only I could figure out
who this P-Star7 is.
- 如果我能弄清楚就好了
这个P-Star7是谁。
- Hello.
- 你好。
[indistinct conversation]
[含糊不清的对话]
- P-Star7 is my new hero.
- P-Star7 是我的新英雄。
- Hey, that's me.
- 嘿，那是我。
- Yeah, right.
- 是的，对。
- He really knows
how to complain.
- 他真的知道
如何投诉。
- But I wasn't com--
- 但我没能——
- P-Star7 is cool
because he's anonymous.
- P-Star7 很酷
因为他是匿名的。
- Oh, yeah.
- 哦，是的。
He's cool
because he's a nanny mouse.
他很酷
因为他是一只老鼠保姆。
- You may not like
what P-Star7 has to say,
- 你可能不喜欢
P-Star7 必须说的话
but you have to agree
that he keeps it real.
但你必须同意
他保持真实。
He's a true hero
for our troubled times.
他是一个真正的英雄
为了我们的困难时期。
- Well, I'll just have
to make my Krabby Patties better
- 好吧，我就拥有
让我的蟹黄饼变得更好
so P-Star7 will like 'em.
所以 P-Star7 会喜欢他们的。
*
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
[grill sizzling]
[烧烤滋滋作响]
No, it's not round enough.
不，它不够圆。
Maybe just a little
off the edge here.
也许只是一点点
离开这里的边缘。
*
No, now the other side
is wobbly.
不，现在另一边
摇摇欲坠。
I'll just even it up
a little here.
我会把它弄平
这里有一点。
*
Now it's smaller than that one.
现在比那个小了。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Oh.
哦。
Hey, Squidward.
- Yes?
嘿，章鱼哥。
- 是的？
- Has P-Star7 responded
to my nice note yet?
- P-Star7 回复了吗
我的好便条还没收到吗？
- Oh, he responded hours ago.
- 哦，他几个小时前就回复了。
- Why didn't you tell me?
- 你为什么不告诉我？
- Because I don't care?
- 因为我不在乎？
[crowd murmuring]
[人群窃窃私语]
- That's for me.
- 那是给我的。
- His vituperative hyperbole
- 他的谩骂式的夸张
has certainly diminished
your credibility.
确实减少了
你的信誉。
- Oh, why did you
have to say that?
- 哦，你为什么
必须这么说吗？
- You're right.
- 你说得对。
I should have put it
on the bulletin board instead.
我应该把它
而是在公告板上。
"Signed, HandsomeLad42."
“签名，帅哥42号。”
- You may be handsome,
HandsomeLad42,
- 你可能很帅，
帅哥42，
but you're very mean.
但你很刻薄。
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]
- Yeah, that's a good one, yeah.
- 是的，这是一件好事，是的。
You know, all this note-writing
你知道，所有这些笔记
must be making you folks hungry.
一定让你们饿了。
We have a short line
at the register.
我们有一条短线
在登记处。
- [snoring]
- [打鼾]
- I brought a bag lunch.
- 我带了袋午餐。
- [stammering]
Wait a second.
- [结巴]
等一下。
None of you
bulletin-board browsers
你们都没有
公告板浏览器
are buying me patties?
给我买肉饼吗？
- Why would we buy food
from a place
- 我们为什么要买食物
从一个地方
that "smells like
stinky armpits"?
那个“闻起来像
腋窝臭”？
- What?
- 什么？
[sniffing]
[嗅嗅]
That's not true.
那不是真的。
- Hey, it's on the board.
- 嘿，它在黑板上。
- And the board is never wrong.
- 董事会永远不会错。
- Does anyone need to buy a pen?
- 有人需要买钢笔吗？
How about some paper?
来点纸怎么样？
[groans]
[呻吟]
- [crying]
- [哭泣]
- What's wrong?
- 怎么了？
- It's this P-Star7.
- 这是P-Star7。
He's been saying
terrible things about me
他一直在说
关于我的可怕的事情
and the Krusty Krab.
和蟹堡王。
- Oh, I think they were
all good things.
- 哦，我想他们是
所有美好的事物。
- Not good.
- 不好。
He said the Krusty Krab
他说蟹堡王
made him feel
dark and empty inside.
让他感觉
里面又黑又空。
- Well, he probably meant
- 嗯，他可能是说
his stomach was dark and empty,
他的胃又黑又空，
and he was hungry for more.
他还渴望更多。
- No, a master of acid wit
like P-Star7
- 不，是一位尖刻的机智大师
像P-Star7
would never express himself
so clumsily.
永远不会表达自己
如此笨拙。
He called me Cry-Baby139.
他叫我Cry-Baby139。
- You were Fry-Banshee?
- 你是弗莱女妖？
- Yeah.
- 是的。
- Well, maybe he just thought
- 好吧，也许他只是想
it was funny,
很有趣，
and--and when he said
that Krabby Patties
然后——当他说
那个蟹肉饼
taste like old baseball gloves--
尝起来像旧棒球手套——
- He said that?
- 他这么说的？
- Oh, not yet.
- 哦，还没有。
*
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
Taste like old baseball gloves,
do they?
味道像旧棒球手套，
他们吗？
- [laughing]
- [笑]
I don't know
who this P-Star7 is,
我不知道
这个P-Star7是谁，
but he's brilliant.
但他很聪明。
- He's a diabolical genius,
that's what he is.
- 他是一个恶魔般的天才
他就是这样。
- [murmuring]
- [低语]
- Mr. Krabs,
the grill's gone cold.
- 蟹老板先生，
烤架变冷了。
- Nobody's ordering, son.
- 没有人点菜，孩子。
It's that cursed corkboard.
就是那个该死的软木板。
I'm gonna take it down.
It's nothing but trouble.
我要把它拿下来。
没什么，就是麻烦。
- You can't, Mr. Krabs.
It's for the community.
- 你不能，蟹老板。
这是为了社区。
I still believe in the power
of the bulletin board.
我仍然相信力量
的公告板。
[crowd laughing]
[人群大笑]
- "You smell."
- “你闻起来。”
[crowd laughing]
[人群大笑]
- "One of your eyes is too big."
- “你的一只眼睛太大了。”
[crowd laughing]
[人群大笑]
- "Close your mouth
when you eat."
-“闭上你的嘴
当你吃饭的时候。”
- [burps]
- [打嗝]
Oh.
哦。
- Oh, "This picture looks like
- 哦，“这张照片看起来像
it was drawn by a brine shrimp!"
是丰年虾拉来的！”
[crying]
Oh, Daddy.
[哭泣]
哦，爸爸。
- [laughing]
- [笑]
Huh?
啊？
"Squidward Tentacles
“章鱼哥的触手
"should never be allowed
“永远不应该允许
"behind a cash register.
“在收银机后面。
P-Star7."
P-Star7。”
Oh, that is it.
哦，就是这样。
Why can't any of these yokels
为什么这些乡巴佬不能
understand I'm working here
ironically?
了解我在这里工作
讽刺的是？
- Oh, sure you are.
- 哦，当然是。
P-Star7 has your number,
all right.
P-Star7 有你的电话号码，
好吧。
- I'm gonna give you
a number...
- 我会给你
一个数字...
of contusions!
挫伤！
[crowd cheering]
[人群欢呼]
- People, can't you see
what's happened?
- 各位，你们难道看不出来吗？
发生了什么事？
This bulletin board has become
该公告栏已成为
a bullying board.
欺凌委员会。
[crowd murmuring]
[人群窃窃私语]
- Okay that's it.
- 好吧，就是这样。
Everybody out.
大家都出去吧。
- I can't believe
we're being kicked out again.
- 我不敢相信
我们又被赶出去了。
Let's go to my house.
我们去我家吧。
*
- Oh, P-Star7 is bringing out
the worst in everybody.
- 哦，P-Star7 即将推出
每个人中最糟糕的。
I'd like to send him a message.
我想给他发消息。
- We'll teach him a lesson
he'll never forget.
- 我们会教训他的
他永远不会忘记。
- A lesson in polite manners.
- 礼貌礼仪课程。
- Or we could push him
off a cliff.
- 或者我们可以推他
掉下悬崖。
- Ooh, excellent option,
Mr. Squidward.
- 哦，很棒的选择，
章鱼哥先生。
- We have to find out
who this P-Star7 is.
-我们必须找出答案
这个P-Star7是谁。
Gentlemen, I propose
a stakeout.
先生们，我提议
监视。
[crickets chirping]
[蟋蟀鸣叫]
Pineapple One to Mad Daddy.
菠萝一号给疯爸爸。
Come in, Mad Daddy.
进来吧，疯狂的爸爸。
[static]
[静止的]
- This is Mad Daddy.
- 这是疯爸爸。
I read you, Pineapple One.
我读到你了，菠萝一号。
Any movement?
有什么动静吗？
[static]
[静止的]
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
- Negatory.
- 否定。
Pineapple One
to Delicate Flower.
菠萝一号
到娇嫩的花。
Come in, Delicate Flower.
进来吧，娇花。
- I am not answering
to Delicate Flower!
- 我不回答
致娇花！
[soft instrumental music]
[轻柔的器乐]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Shh.
Maintain radio silence.
- 嘘。
保持无线电静默。
Wait a minute.
I see something.
等一下。
我看到一些东西。
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
*
- Ooh.
- 哦。
[slurping]
[发出声音]
- So that's what happens
to the ketchup stains.
- 所以这就是发生的事情
番茄酱污渍。
*
- Surprise, P-Star7!
- 惊喜，P-Star7！
all: Patrick?
所有人：帕特里克？
- [growling]
- [咆哮]
I'll tear you to pieces.
我会把你撕成碎片。
[growling]
[咆哮]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[munching]
[咀嚼]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[machinery whirring]
[机器的呼呼声]
*
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
- Patrick.
- 帕特里克.
You're P-Star7?
你是P-Star7吗？
- Well, that's what my last note
was about, SpongeBob.
- 嗯，这就是我最后的笔记
是关于海绵宝宝。
I was upset that people
take everything I say
我很沮丧人们
接受我所说的一切
the wrong way.
错误的方式。
- So when you said
that Krabby Patties
- 所以当你说
那个蟹肉饼
reminded you
of old baseball gloves,
提醒你了
旧棒球手套，
you really meant
that they gave you the feeling
你的意思是
他们给你的感觉
of your carefree youth.
属于你无忧无虑的青春。
- [munching]
- [咀嚼]
Yeah, I think.
是的，我想。
- You hear that, Boardy?
- 你听到了吗，博迪？
It wasn't you.
It was never you.
不是你。
从来都不是你。
We were the monsters all along.
我们一直都是怪物。
- Well, I'm still angry!
- 好吧，我还是很生气！
And I need something
to calm me down.
我需要一些东西
让我平静下来。
Ooh, this knitting circle
ought to do the trick.
哦，这个编织圈
应该可以解决问题。
And you all are joining me.
你们都加入了我。
Especially you, Delicate Flower.
尤其是你，娇花。
- Oh, ratfish.
- 哦，鼠鱼。
- Pineapple One to Knit Mama.
- 给妈妈编织的菠萝一号。
Can I needle you
for a little more yarn?
我可以给你打针吗
多一点纱线吗？
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
- Oh, brother.
- 哦，兄弟。
Please bring back P-Star7.
请带回P-Star7。
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]